[{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664035542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":9036,"timeElapsed":46395},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664041923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6380,"timeElapsed":52776},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664051896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":9971,"timeElapsed":62749},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664056712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4815,"timeElapsed":67565},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664061852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5139,"timeElapsed":72705},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664067586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5732,"timeElapsed":78439},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664072892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5305,"timeElapsed":83745},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664075418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":86271},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664077994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":88847},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664086509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7131,"timeElapsed":97362},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664090887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4377,"timeElapsed":101740},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664094675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3787,"timeElapsed":105528},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664097759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":3082,"timeElapsed":108611},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664101121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3362,"timeElapsed":111974},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664104205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3082,"timeElapsed":115058},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664107684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3478,"timeElapsed":118537},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664109929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2244,"timeElapsed":120782},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664112010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":122863},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":14027,"timeElapsed":137844},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3809,"timeElapsed":141654},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2334,"timeElapsed":143989},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664138000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4862,"timeElapsed":148853},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664140380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2380,"timeElapsed":151233},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664142553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2171,"timeElapsed":153406},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":156276},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664149361,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3937,"timeElapsed":160214},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3177,"timeElapsed":163392},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664158965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5447,"timeElapsed":169818},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3417,"timeElapsed":173236},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664164612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2228,"timeElapsed":175465},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664166729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2117,"timeElapsed":177582},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664169329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2598,"timeElapsed":180182},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664171550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2220,"timeElapsed":182403},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2161,"timeElapsed":184565},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664176198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2485,"timeElapsed":187051},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":189018},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7027,"timeElapsed":196889},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664190954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4917,"timeElapsed":201807},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664197198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":6243,"timeElapsed":208051},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2576,"timeElapsed":210628},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2659,"timeElapsed":213288},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205084,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":215937},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":218665},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2512,"timeElapsed":221178},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664213199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":224052},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":9037,"timeElapsed":234154},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2925,"timeElapsed":237081},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":240457},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1735,"timeElapsed":242193},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":245865},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1825,"timeElapsed":247691},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2293,"timeElapsed":249985},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2761,"timeElapsed":252747},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2991,"timeElapsed":255739},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7235,"timeElapsed":263984},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2565,"timeElapsed":266550},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3316,"timeElapsed":269867},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664261360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2346,"timeElapsed":272213},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4160,"timeElapsed":276374},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3103,"timeElapsed":279478},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":282264},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664273819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":284672},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664277956,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4135,"timeElapsed":288808},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4509,"timeElapsed":293319},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664290536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7089,"timeElapsed":301389},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3369,"timeElapsed":304759},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":308047},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664301580,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4384,"timeElapsed":312433},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2678,"timeElapsed":315111},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664306342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2083,"timeElapsed":317195},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309563,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3219,"timeElapsed":320416},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664312793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3229,"timeElapsed":323646},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3159,"timeElapsed":326806},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"195","question":"Did you play any sports growing up? If multiple, which was your favorite? Do you still play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2119,"timeElapsed":328926},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":10272,"timeElapsed":340206},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4601,"timeElapsed":344808},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664336359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2403,"timeElapsed":347212},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":349305},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664341172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":352025},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664343910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2737,"timeElapsed":354763},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664346530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2619,"timeElapsed":357383},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664349360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2829,"timeElapsed":360213},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1991,"timeElapsed":362205},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6200,"timeElapsed":369373},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3857,"timeElapsed":373231},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664366828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4449,"timeElapsed":377681},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2613,"timeElapsed":380296},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664371809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2365,"timeElapsed":382662},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2449,"timeElapsed":385112},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3333,"timeElapsed":388445},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3183,"timeElapsed":391629},{"subjectID":"qhnsuwbbdc","prolificID":"55cce6ea34e90600058d1e6d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742164d96ddca2452a3e54","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2019,"timeElapsed":393649}]